Guide to the Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Files, Series I; 4; (4 boxes)
  - File 16 (Box 2, Folder 38-40)
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). INTERNATIONAL DAYS OF PROTEST AGAINST THE WAR IN VIETNAM
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). WHY ARE WE DEMONSTRATING? Illustrated.
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). TELEGRAM TO PRESIDENT JOHNSON.
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). WHY STRIKE?...THATS WHY!
    - WARMTH (in red) on blue illustrated stock. Concert / light show at Pauley Ballroom poster
    - WE ARE CONDUCTING A STUDY FOR A SOCIOLOGY COURSE 2 leaves.
    - WEDDING / two strangers in town (purple ink)
    - WHO ARE LOS SIETE (yellow stock)
    - YAF ELECTIONS RUSE: THE SO-CALLED GATOR PARTY
    - YSA-COE (org). SUPPORT STATE!
  - File 17 (Box 14, Folder 328)
    - DESIDERATA. Found text reprinted from Max Ehrmanns poems, 1927, renewed 1954, reprinted by permission of Crescendo, published by MJ Hobbs / Walton on Thames
    - Diego Rivera print on p. 15 of an unnamed source. Probably displayed during Free Speech Movement of Viet Nam War protests.
    - Holt publisher in NYC (org). DID THE BERKELEY RIOTS START WITH THE BOSTON TEA PARTY? Large poster advertising Holt publications.
    - INSTRUCTIONS TO ALL PERSONS OF JAPANESE ANCESTRY. De Witts April 22, 1942 directive (Presidio of SF issue) reprinted by Collectors Items Shop in Berkeley. Creased.
    - IT BECAME NECESSARY TO DESTROY THE TOWN TO SAVE IT Photo by Paul Avery. Printed by East Wind.
    - McClure (Michael) BERKELEY SONG. Broadside poem. Printed by Wesley Tanner [Arif Press] for Moes Books [on Telegraph Avenue] for the New Year 1988.
    - Poetry reading. MICHAEL McCLURE in San Diego. Signed in print by artist. Friday December 12, 1969.
    - PSYCHEDELIA / THE CLASSIC POSTER BOOK. NY: Mallard Press / Octopus Books (1990). Grateful Dead poster on cover.
    - RALPH ELLISON: An American Journey. Poster for documentary film by Avon Kirkland.
    - Real Free Press #1 (November 1968)
    - Real Free Press #2 (Sept 1969)
    - Real Free Press #3 (Dec 1970)
    - Real Free Press #4 ( October 1971)
    - Real Free Press #5 (March 1972)
    - ROY HAROLD SWANSON gravestone, children playing with guns. Poster from photograph.
    - SOUTH AFRICA WILL BE FREEW. Poster in orange, green, black and white.
    - VIETNAMIZATION, photograph by Paul Avery, printed by East Wind, in black and white.
    - VIETNAMIZATION, photograph by Paul Avery, printed by East Wind, in black and light green (variant colors)
    - WE WORK FOR PEACE (dove and white on blue pasted over larger poster), VIETNAM MARCH, Nov 16, 1969
  - File 18 (Box 2, Folder 41-43)
    - A HOME FOR PEACE (blue silk screen art).
    - Ad Hoc Committee for Student Rights (org). HEYNS: THE SILENT CHANCELLOR
    - Affirmative Action AD (org). DEAR FRIEND= open letter + (attached) AFFIRMATIVE ACTION Proposed text of the Affirmative Action ad.
    - AFL-CIO (org). FOUR WEEKS FOR JUSTICE.
    - African Peoples Socialist Party (org). PEOPLES DEMOCRATIC UHURU MOVEMENT.
    - Ally (The) (org). HELP THE ANTI-WAR GIs HELP THEMSELVES: SUPPORT THE ALLY.
    - AN OPEN LETTER TO THE CAMPUS COMMUNITY. Numerous professors and students sign.
    - ARE YOU READY FOR THE CLASS REVOLUTION? Yellow stock.
    - ASUC (org) Labor Committee, members of Womens Liberation (org). WE NEED YOUR BODIES* (in re Tenneco strike)
    - BAY AREA SOLIDARITY BULLETIN Number 1 (March, 1982). Self-wrs, (22) pp. Illustrated.
    - Bay Area Spartacist Committee (org). GEOFF WHITE FOR BERKELEY CITY COUNCILWHY YOU SHOULD VOTE SOCIALIST. Pink stock.
    - Berkeley Liberation Farm (org). WELCOME HOME, 8pp.
    - Better Berkeley Council. DEAR FELLOW SUFFERER= open letter. Yellow stock.
    - Black Panther Party (et al). (orgs). DTOP THE SAN QUENTIN RAILROAD. Illustrated.
    - Black Panther Party (et al). INTERNATIONAL COMMITTEE TO DEFEND ELDRIDGE CLEAVER / AN EVENING WITH THE DEFENSE COMMITTEE
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Revolutionary Union (org) KENNY HORSTON, Chairman of Black Panther Caucus speaks.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Revolutionary Union (org). FILMSFILMS STRUGGLE / INTERVIEW WITH BOBBY SEALEIllustrated.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + William Brent Defense Fund (org). SET BILL BRENT FREENOW!! Brent was Captain of Black Panther Party.
    - Black Panther Party (org) THURSDAY IS THE DAY / FREE BOBBY Ball / dance benefit. Yellow stock.
    - Black Panther Party (org). Nower (Ellie) DEAR= open letter, personalized for the Litwacks. Purple ink. PhD candidate in history at University of California, Berkeley = Litwacks Dept. Of black-white relationships & invitation to her home for give-and-take session with representative of The Black Panther Party.
    - Black Panther Party (org). SOLERDAD BROTHERS LEGAL COMMITTEE.
    - Black Panther Party (org). THE TRIAL OF BOBBY & ERICKASCHEER FOR CONGRESS
    - Buff stock.
    - CAL Christian Fellowship (org) HOW TO CHANGE THE POWER STRUCTURE. Green stock.
    - CAL Conservatives for Political Action (org). PIRATE QUEEN OF CAPITALISM HEROINE. Of Britt Wadner, Swedish radio broadcaster from the seas. Blue ink. Reprint from Liberal Innovator.
    - Californians for Liberal Representation (org). HEAR SENATOR WAYNE MORSEon VIETNAM
    - Campus Friends of AFT 1570 (org) AFT LOCAL 1570- AFL/CIO ON STRIKE. Illustrated.
    - Campus Friends of AFT 1570 (org). TWLF & AFT SOLIDARITY DAY.
    - Campus Friends of AFT 1570 (org). CAN THIS BE NORMAL CAMPUS LIFE Yellow stock.
    - Campus Friends of AFT 1570 (org). ON STRIKESTRIKE NOW!
    - Center for Participant Education (CPE) A MESSAGE TO THE NON-STRIKING STUDENTS. Illustrated. 4pp.
    - Center for Participant Education (org sponsored by the University of California, Berkeley student body = ASUC). A MESSAGE TO NON-STRIKING STUDENTS, No. 2. Illustrated. 4pp.
    - Chicano Defense Fund (org). ON AUGUST THE 29th
    - Christian Revolutionary Medical Committees (sub-org). THE ABOLITION OF MANCAN MAN SURVIVEWILL YOU SURVIVE. Blue stock.
    - Christian World Liberation Front (org) AND AFTER THIS WAR?....RADICALIZE THE REVOLUTIONARY MOVEMENT!! Red ink on light green stock.
    - Committee of 100 (org). UNADILLA, GEORGIA.(first black high school graduate = Roy Lee Hunter). Yellow and black, with mailer.
    - Committee of Concerned Asian Scholars (org) + Law Students of UC (org) + History Community (org) + Boalt Hall Action Fund Legislation Committee (org) DO YOU STILL BELIEVE IN THE WART. 4 leaves, stapled.
    - Committee on New Alternatives in the Mid-East (org). Arie Bober, Israeli Socialist speaking tour. Red ink on pink stock.
    - Committee to Abolish Prison Slavery (org). HISTORY OF THE COMMITTEE, 12pp. 1977.
    - Committee to Abolish Prison Slavery (org). THE ABOLITIONIST. [POSITION PAPER], 6pp.
    - Communist Party of Northern California (org). ON VIOLENCE. Anti-advocacy of violence, force, terrorism or member informers
    - CORE (Berkeley campus org). LOUISIANA SUMMUER PROJECT, 4pp, illustrated.
    - Country Joe and the Fish (music group) FISH FREAKS: THIS IS YOUR CHANCEBerkeleys Best Band! Event flyer
    - CPLA / PLP / PL Forum on Racism (orgs). CARLA ROEMER WILL SPEAK.
    - CPLP (org) PL FORUM / THE COMMUNIST VIEW. Puerto Rican speaker. Yellow stock.
    - Criminology Students Association (org). COMMUNITY CONTROL OF POLICE. Buff stock.
    - DefendAffAction (org). PROFESSORS DECLARE SUPPORT
    - Emergency Response Network (org). THE PLEDGE OF RESISTANCE
    - ESCAPE TO CANADA. Illustrated booklet, 16pp.
    - FACHRES-CA (org) WHY IS THE UNITED STATES AT WAR WITH NICARAGUA? Three leaves.
    - Fellowship of Reconciliation (org). A PROMISE OF RESISTANCE
    - Fruehan (George J.) University of California, Berkeley senior. SOLUTION OR DIVERSION? (another copy elsewhere in archive, but here, with, apparently:), page 2: WE AS STUDENTS = 5 points.
    - GI SAC Berkeley (org). APRIL 6 / GI-CIVILIAN PEACE MARCH (EASTER PEACE MARCH). Illustrated.
    - Hiroshima Day Committee (org) HIROSHIMA DAY. Illustrated. 25th Anniversary.
    - International Socialists (Berkeley Campus and Berkeley Community Branches) (orgs). END THE WAR! SMASH THE WAR PARTIES!
    - Josephson (Matthew) THE BIG GUNS. Offprint from The Nation, 12 pp, self-wrappers.
    - MASC (University of California, Berkeley org). THE CAMPUS RESISTANCE. Green stock. BOYCOTT GRAPES.
    - MASS MEETING TONIGHTWHAT SHOULD WE DO TONIGHT? After police tear-gassing students.
    - Militant Labor Forum (org). IS THE ANTI-WAR MOVEMENTANTI-IMPERIALIST? Red ink.
    - Militant Labor Forum (org). THE STRUGGLE FOR WOMENS LIBERATION. Red ink.
    - NO BUSINESS AS USUALSTOP THE WAR!. Illustrated.
    - One to One (org). Grigsby (Channing) ONE TO ONE (sex relationships)
    - Organization of American Historians (org). Flyer for new periodical, Magazine of History. Free Speech photograph on cover.
    - Peace and Fredom Party. AFTER CHICAGO: WHAT IS TO BE DONE? Green stock, illustrated.
    - Peace Brigade (org) + Resistance (org). NATIONAL ANTI-DRAFT DAY IS WEDNESDAY, JUNE 10. Buff stock.
    - Peace Brigade (org). PRESENTS SUMMER SESSIONS ON NONVIOLENT REVOLUTION. Buff stock.
    - Progressive Labor Party (org) ESCALATION AT HOME (illustrated).
    - Progressive Labor Party. DONT VOTE! ORGANIZE. Illustrated.
    - PROTEST UC NUCLEAR WEAPONS RESEARCH AT LIVERMORE. Map. free donuts.
    - Re-education Center in SF (org). PRESENTATION & ENTERTAINMENT. Pink stock.
    - RIBOFLAVIN IS IN YOUR BODY! Beer design. Dance poster. Yellow stock.
    - RSU (org) SOLIDARITY DEMONSTRATION. Illustrated.
    - RSU Steering Committee (org). STUDENTS CHALLENGE THE FACULTY / ADMINISTRATION AND REGENTS
    - RSU. INVITATION TO THE TRIAL (of Stew Albert)
    - RSU. SUPPORT THE STRIKE!
    - SCLC (org). SOME IMPORTANT FACTS ABOUT SCLC
    - SDS (Berkeley campus org). SUPPORT THE BLACK STUDENTS. Blue stock.
    - SDS (Berkeley campus) (org). FACULTY ON STRIKE.
    - SDS (Berkeley Campus). STRIKE DEMANDS. Yellow stock.
    - SDS (Joe Hill Collective). STEEL FOR THE STRUGGLE.
    - SDS, No. Calif (org). NO MORATORIUM ON FIGHTING IMPERIALISM-SUPPORT G.E. STRIKERS.
    - SDS. DONT MOURN. ORGANIZE. Songs. Yellow stock.
    - SDS. DEFEAT US IMPERIALISM / verso: SUPPORT THE IRANIAN PEOPLE.. Buff stock.
    - SDS. THE MORATORIUM IS A COVER, NOT A SOLUTION. Jay Sargeant et al. 4pp.
    - SDS. US STEAL OFF CAMPUS.
    - Second Page (The). (distributing and publishing org). FREEDOM?? Green stock.
    - SF State Legal Defense Committee (org). LAWYERS ATTACK POLITICAL REPRESSION IN THE COURTS. Illustrated. Blue stock.
    - Slate (University of California, Berkeley student org). SLATE CANDIDATES. Red, black inks.
    - SMC (org). RALLYFOR THE VIETNAM MORATORIUM
    - STUDENT LIFE. Full page cartoon / event (?)
    - Student Mobilization Committee (org). ANTIWAR TEACH-IN. Illustrated. Green stock.
    - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in S.E. Asia (org). MARCH SAN FRANCISCO / WASHINGTON DC APRIL 24. Illustrated. Yellow stock.
    - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (org). NOV. 14 / NATIONAL STUDENT STRIKE. Illustrated.
    - Student Mobilization Committee. VIETNAM WEEK EVENTS FOR THUR.
    - SUPPORT OUR OWN. Tenure question. Blue stock.
    - Third World Faculty (University of California, Berkeley) = TWLF3 (org) ALL FACULTY CONVOCATION
    - Third World Liberation Front (org) + Non-Academic UC Employees Committee (org). REPORT / THIRD WORLD LIBERATION FRONT
    - Third World Liberation Front (org). QUESTIONNAIRE
    - THIS IS POLICE BRUTALITY / verso:
    - UC Black Cultural Center (org). Three page info sheet / URBAN RESEARCH & PUBLIC SERVICE PROGRAM / SOURCE OF FUNDS AND USE OF FUNDS.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). INSTRUCTS ITS COMMITTEE ON UNIVERSITY WELFARE.
    - University of California, Berkeley. AFT 1570. (org). THE THREAT TO OUR COMMUNITY. Yellow stock. President Kerr was fired.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Associated Graduate Council (org). POSITION PAPER ON OBSCENITY.in re use of obscene language politically (etc)should not be allowed.
    - University of California, Berkeley. ASUC (student body org). GCC IS FOR APPROPRIATING YOUR ASUC FUNDS
    - University of California, Berkeley. Bancroft Library (org). PRESENTS / TAKING PART. Free Speech photograph on cover. Events program.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Berkeley Faculty Union AFT 1474. TO: ALL FACULTY. NOTICE OF AN OPEN MEETING TO DISCUSS (disputes that may arise between students, staff, faculty, administration, and supporting all faculty during this period of NO BUSINESS AS USUAL.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Dept. of History (org). COLLOQUIM. Litwack et al.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Faculty Peace Committee (org). DEAR COLLEAGUE= open letter signed by Richard Strohman in type.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Faculty Peace Committee (org). STOP THE BOMBING / A LETTER TO PRESIDENT JOHNSON.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Faculty Union, AFT 1474 (org). TO THE FACULTY
    - University of California, Berkeley. GCC (Graduate Coordinating Committee (org) DECEMBER 8 / THE ACADEMIC SENATE VOTES
    - University of California, Berkeley. Graduate Coordinating Committee (org). GETTING BIGGER & GETTING BETTER. Purple ink.
    - University of California, Berkeley. History Department (org). HISTORY COMMUNITY COMMITTEE INFORMATION SHEET.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Sociology Graduate Club (org). PASSED THE FOLLOWING RESOLUTIONS purple ink.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Sociology Graduate Students (group). RECOMMENDATION TO THE SOCIOLOGY FACULTY. Purple ink.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Steering Committee, Berkeley Faculty Alliance (org). A LETTER TO PRESIDENT JOHNSON
    - University of California, BerkeleyCYSC (org). ECOLOGY: A MARXIST VIEW Illustrated.
    - United Campus Ministry. ANGUISH OF VIETNAM. Blue stock.
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). PICKET PRESIDENT JOHNSON. Buff stock.
    - WHO ARE LOS SIETE?
    - Workers for Peoples Democracy (org). WHAT AMERICAN WORKERS KNOW ABOUT THE DOOMSDAY THEORY. Buff stock.
    - Workers fort Peoples Democracy (org) CONSCIENCE AND THE ANTI-WAR MOVEMENT. Tan stock.
    - Workers League (org). ALL TROOPS OUT NOW! Illustrated.
    - Young Socialist Alliance (org). JOIN THE YOUNG SOCIALIST ALLIANCE
    - Young Socialist Alliance (org). National Executive CommitteeYSA PROGRAM FOR THE CAMPUS REVOLT (illustrated), 4pp.
    - YPSL. DAILY CAL IS UNFAIR. On green stock.
  - File 19 (Box 2, Folder 44-46)
    - AFT (org). TAXATION WITHOUT REPRESENTATION (on tuition)
    - AFT Local 1474 (org). FACULTY MEMBERS large broadside Enrollment message and coupon.
    - American Civil Liberties Union, So Cal (org). BIOGRAPHICAL SKETCH OF HUGH R. MANES
    - Battersby, Wofsy and Zelnik three University of California, Berkeley professors. ON JANUARY 29.in support of young men resisting the draft, on occasion of arraignment of Benjamin Spock et al in Boston. Purple ink.
    - Bay Area Coalition Against the Bakke Decision (org). BAY AREA COALITION AGAINST THE BAKKE DECISION. Orange stock.
    - Bay Area Coalition Against the Bakke Decision (org). DEFEND MINORITY ASMISSIONS / PROTEST THE BAKKE DECISION!
    - Bay Area Peace Council (org). MARCH IN SAN FRANCISCOTO BRING ALL THE TROOPS HOME NOW Red image.
    - Berkeley Campus International Socialists (org) WHY OUST ROTC? (illustrated)
    - Berkeley Draft Information Committee (org). Sponsors at home of Professor and Mrs. Stephan Smale, a party: LETS HAVE A BASH. Illustrated. At their home.
    - Berkeley Free Press (org) PRESENTS A BENEFIT Country Joe & The Fist; play by Marvin Norinsky. Psychedelic lettering. Illustrated.
    - Black Panther Party (org) HUEY NEWTON / FREEDOM FIGHTER.PEACE & FREEDOM FORUM.FREE HUEY. Panther image.
    - Black Panther Party (org) & SF Mime Troupe (org) SEIZE THE TIME / SONS OF REVOLUTION. Illustrated. Mime Troupe re-enacts episodes in history of the BPP. Bobby Seale quote. Orange stock.
    - Black Panther Party (org) / White Panthers (org). SHOOT YOUR SHOT (poem). Platform of White Panthers, 10 points. Point 1: Full support and endorsement of Black Panther Partys Ten-point Program Illustrated.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + April 27 Mobilization Committee (org). MARCH AND RALLY April 27 SF. Illustrated in blue. Bobby Seale spoke / Muhammad Ali was present. Map and text on verso
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Free Speech Movement (org) MEMORIAL MEETING FOR BOBBY HUTTON. Friday April 12. Killed by Oakland police, April 6, 1968. With his image. On verso: FREE ELDRIDGE CLEAVER + text
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Peace and Freedom Movement (org). Page 3 of a document likely present elsewhere in the archive, here continuing with part of Paragraph C and adding Paragraphs D & E. NB!!! Belongs with pages 1-2 County Council Meeting in folder 23
    - Black Panther Party (org) + Socialist Camnpaign Committee, Campus YSA (org). MEMORIAL FOR MALCOLM X. Panther image. Cleaver and Newton spoke. Berkeley.
    - Black Panther Party (org) and Peace and Freedom Party (org). NOTES ON THE BLACK PANTHER PARTY FOR SELF DEFENSE AND THE PEACE AND FREEDOM MOVEMENT, 3pp.
    - Black Panther Party (org) INTERNATIONAL COMMITTEE TO DEFEND ELDRIDGE CLEAVERTO GOVERNOR REAGANin re THE REVOCATION OF CLEAVERS PAROLE.
    - Black Panther Party (org) INTERNATIONAL COMMITTEE TO DEFEND ELDRIDGE CLEAVER. DEAR FRIEND= open letter signed by Robert Scheer, Editor-in-Chief, Ramparts Magazine.
    - Black Panther Party (org). FREE HUEY WORKSHOP. Panther image.
    - Black Panther Party (org). MAY 1 NEW HAVEN CONNECTICUT / MAY DAY / WEEKEND GATHERING TO SHOW SOLIDARITY FOR PANTHER PRISONERS OF WAR. David Hilliard, BPP Chief of Staff spoke. Texts on verso.
    - Black Panther Party (org). POWER TO THE PEOPLE. Committee on Public Safety [City of Berkeley?] in re tonights meeting with Eldridge Cleaver.
    - Black Panther Party (org). RALLY. Black on red. Poorly or intentionally [mis-] printed
    - Campus Movement for a New America (org) PAUL KRASSNER appearance. Illustrated. Purple ink. With Country Joe and the Fish.
    - East Bay Socialist Forum (org) + YSA (org) CHE LIVES! Illustrated. Many Chicano speakers.
    - El Partido de Paz y Libertad (org) Event / Endorsement of candidates Romo for governor, Buckley, Scheer, Scahill.
    - First Congressional District Write In Committee for Phil Drath (org). PEACE Illustrated. Grateful Dead appeared.
    - Free Speech Movement / Alameda County Council (org). ANNOUNCEMENTS (a duplicate?), 2pp.
    - G.T.U. Peace Center (org). Graduate Theological Union Church Contact Committee (org). Four Contacts. Purple ink.
    - Graduate Womens Sociology Caucus, Womens Faculty Group, AFSCME Local 1695 (org) BREAKING THE SHACKLES / CONFERENCE ON WOMEN:
    - Green (Simon) TO MEMBERS OF THE HISTORY DEPARTMENT. Purple ink. In re the draft.
    - Hamilton (Roger) LT, USA Navy, (resigned)Grad Student, University of California, Berkeley, Comp. Lit. DEAR FACULTY MEMBER= open letter. By a Vietnam War veteran.
    - INFORMATION FOR NOVICE STREET FIGHTERS, 4pp.
    - Iranian Students Association and Arab Students Association (org). AN ORGANIZATION BANNED FROM CAMPUS. WANTED OFF [NGUYEN CAO] KY. Illustrated. Verso: MARCH WITH THE ANTI-IMPERIALIST CONTINGENT!
    - JOHN GEORGE FOR CONGRESS. Black candidate. 14 UC professors endorse. Tan stock. With POSITION PAPER attached + pledge sheet = 4 leaves.
    - League of Women Voters of Berkeley (org) DID HE LIVE IN VAIN? [of Martin Luther King, Jr].
    - Leviathan, A New Movement Monthly. Prospectus and envelope. Illustrated.
    - MAPS / GCC (org). MAPS REPORTS
    - Martin Luther King, Jr (assassinatiuon of) + Peace and Fredom Party (contra). IN THE AFTERMATH OF THE DEATH OF MARTIN LUTHER KING = original TS on yellow stock, disassociating ourselves from a Peace and Freedom Party demonstration / march to Oakland jail, as that act by the Party is deemed cynical & exploitative. By Leon Litwack? Notes in margins.
    - MAY 4 1919 / 1969. PARTICIPATE
    - Memorial Day Hospitality Committee (org). Citizens asked to house visitors. Orange stock.
    - Movement Against Political Suspensions = MAPS = M.A.P.S. (org) NAPS TIME TABLE.
    - NAACP (org) DEAR FRIEND= open letter from Roy Wilkins, Oct 10, 1969.
    - NAACP (org) FULL SPEED AHEAD, speech by Roy Wilkins, Executive Director. Broadside format (folded)
    - NAACP (org) WHO SAID A GOOD CIVIL RIGHTS ORGANIZATION CANT BE MILITANT? .. THE TIME IS NOW-TOMORROW MAY BE TOO LATE., 4pp.
    - NAACP (org) 1967 HOLIDAY SEAL CAMPAIGN, signed by Lena Horne, Chairman, in type. Verso: RIOT PREVENTION.
    - NAACP Legal Defense & Educational Fund (org) DOES GE MAKE YOU MAD? SCARED? GUILTY? Large poster folded, illustrated. Likely a duplicate.
    - NAACP Legal Defense Fund imprint (org). Lewis (Anthony) SCHOOL SEGREGATION / END IT AT ONCE SAY THE SUPREME COURT. Reprinted from the New York Times, Sunday, November 2, 1969.
    - Northern California Emergency Committee Against Racism in Boston (org). CONTINUE THE FIGHT AGAINST RACISM IN BOSTON. / verso: HELP PLAN A MASSIVE RESPONSE TO THE RACIST OFFENSIVE IN BOSTON.
    - Peace and Fredom Party. ALAMEDA COUNTY AREA CHAPTERS, map.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org) ACTING CONVENOR SAM WAINWRIGHT CALLED THE MEETING TO ORDER= first line, 2pp.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org). RESOLUTION ON THE WARSAW STUDENT DEMONSTRATION.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org). WILL THE CITY COUNCIL (of Berkeley) ACT TO END RACISM?
    - Peace and Freedom Movement Structure Committee (org). PROPOSAL FOR OPEN NOMINATIONS Orange stock.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement, SF Labor Committee (org). OPEN LETTER TO MEMBERS OF PEACE & FREEDOM MOVEMENT
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. HELP WANTED. Yellow stock.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. MINORITY REPORT on 18-21 YEAR OLD VOTE, by Joan Wilson.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. PROPOSED CONSTITUTION, 4pp.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. Special Issues Workshop (org) 18 YEAR OLD VOTE INITIATIVE.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement. SUGGESTIONS FOR THE SECOND MEETING 2pp.
    - Peace and Freedom News Volume II:2 (Berkeley, March 31, 1969). 15 cents. 4pp.
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org) REPORT OF CONSTITUTION COMMITTEE, signed in type by Barbara Israel.. 5pp. Founding document.
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org) TO ALL PEACE AND FREEDOM PARTY MEMBERS
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org). PROPOSED BLACK LIBERATION AND NATIONAL MINORITY PLATFORM
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org). WE ARE TRYING TO SET THE PEACE AND FREEDOM PARTY ALOFT= first line. Inscribed for Leon [Litwack]. A few corrections in ink. Three leaves. Text by Lucille Birnbaum, Endorsement Committee
    - Peace and Freedom Party POSITION PAPER OF SUPPORT FOR STOP THE DRAFT WEEK, 2pp.
    - Peace and Freedom Party, Alameda County Council (org). ANNOUNCEMENTS.
    - Peace and Freedom Party. AMENDMENT TO RESOLUTION ON POLISH FREEDOM FIGHTERS
    - Peace and Freedom Party. ANTI-VIUOLENCE STATEMENT by 10 members.
    - Peace and Freedom Party. PARTY in support, with map.
    - Peace and Freedom Party. PROPOSED RULES OF ORDER. Blue stock, 5pp. Founding document.
    - Peace and Freedom Party. SUMMARY CALENDAR.
    - Peace and Freedom Party. THE CONSTITUTIONcontroversial items to be voted on
    - Peoples Park Bail Ball. PARK HERE ANY TIME. Illustrated. Winterland event with Grateful Dead et al.
    - Peoples Park. JOIN THE STRUGGLE. IllustratedPrague / Calif / no admittance
    - Peoples Coalition (org). THE CASE FOR ROTC. Yellow stock.
    - PROPHECY OF A DECLARATION OF INDEPENDENCEBRING JOYLove-pageant rally. Green ink. Un-credited.
    - Radical Student Union (RSU) (org). PRESENTS THE WAY CAME by Peter Watkins (film) etc. Blue stock.